joydress.com 2013-08-21

# Privacy Policy

We value our customers and respects your privacy. We collect information about you in our stores and through our Website in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. As described in this policy, we may share your information among our brands, as may be applicable, and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service. We may also share your information when we are legally required to do so, for example, by court order or in response to a request for information in a civil or criminal proceeding. At our site, our target is to make your shopping experience safe, convenient and care-free. Our privacy and security programs make sure that every transaction made at our site is 100% safe and guaranteed.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**  
The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us. For example, when you wish to purchase a product from this website we may collect details such as your name, address, delivery address and billing address，and other information relevant to your purchase.  
As we are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of "sensitive information", we will assume that you have given consent to the collection of all information you have provided to us for use in accordance with this Statement, unless you tell us otherwise.

 **How Do We Use Cookies?**  
Our Website use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a Website. Cookies enable you to shop on our Website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain Website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our Website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our Website. Cookies may also be used to collect transaction information needed by a scrip or loyalty program to which you have authorized us to provide your personal information.

 **How Do We Collect Information?**  
We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us over the Email, we will not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

 **How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**  
We generally collect your personal information for the following purposes:  
To deliver products you have ordered from us  
To seek your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website.  
Some of the personal information we collect is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service. Other types of personal information we collect help us to develop a profile of who is using our service, this assists us in offering products to suit the needs of the users of this website. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties.**  
We may disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose for which the information was collected or for related purposes, for example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product that you purchased. We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involves the contractor handling personal information we hold. For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:

Deliver products purchased from this website  
Provide electronic funds transfer services, credit card account processing and related services  
In these situations, the third party contractor is strictly from using any prohibited personal information about you except for the specific purpose for which we have supplied. We may also disclose your personal information to various law enforcement agencies and governments around the world for security, customs and immigration purposes. Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorized or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.

 **Security of Your Personal Information.**  
Some browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to connect to our server so you will not have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection. We will securely hold your personal information and we will not trade, rent or sell it. We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system, Firewalls, passwords, anti-virus software and email filters can protect all our electronic information.

 **How Do We Protect Kids' Privacys?**  
We concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our Website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children.

 **Resolving Your Concerns.**  
If you wish to gain access to your personal information, have a complaint about a breach of your privacy or you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used please forward your request, complaint or query to the **[Contact Us](http://www.joydress.com/zouyq/urdressde0925/contact_us.html)**. We will respond to your query or complaint via Email as soon as possible.

 **Changes to This Privacy Statement.**  
We may amend this Privacy Statement as our business requirements or the law changes. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be updated on our site, so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have our most current privacy statement.
